stormpath.com 2017-03-16

# Privacy Policy - Stormpath User Identity API

Your privacy is very important to us at Stormpath and we are committed to protecting it. Please take a moment to read our Privacy Policy below. This Privacy Policy applies to the data collected through the Stormpath Web sites and services, and it describes our practices for collecting and using information and the choices you have.  
Your accessing and continued use of our Web sites signifies your explicit consent to these terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our services change and expand. We will notify you of such changes by posting them on our site. All amendments will be automatically effective 30 days after they are posted.

#### Information We Collect

We may collect personal information about you, such as your name, address and email address and other information that can be used to contact you. We will only collect such information where it is helpful for us to communicate with you, for example to fulfill an order you place, register for a service from us, or provide you with additional information you have requested. Because of the financial nature of our business, our Web sites are not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly request or receive any information from children.  
Like many websites, Stormpath uses cookies on our Web site to collect information anonymously. A cookie is a small bit of information stored by your browser on your hard drive that is used to identify your computer. Cookies collect information like IP addresses and the name of your operating system and browser software, but they do not collect any personal information. Cookies allow us to better serve you when you visit our Web sites, and maintain the quality of interaction when you return to our Web site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

#### Use of your Information

We will not sell, rent, loan or lease your personally information to others unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We will not use or share the personal information that you provide us online in ways unrelated to those described herein without first letting you know and seeking your consent.  
We may use your contact information to tell you about other products we think might interest you. However, if you don’t want us to contact you for promotional purposes, you can tell us when you provide the information. Your contact preferences only apply to marketing contact. We may need to communicate with you regarding the usability of your product or critical messages relating to your service or software (such as service messages, subscription renewal notices, critical notices, or legally mandated notices).  
We use anonymous information, such as that pertaining to web pages viewed, to analyze trends, track users movements, provide a better website experience and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not use this data in a manner that would identify you personally.

#### How We Share Information

We may share your information with our affiliates, consultants, vendors and service providers who assist us in maintaining the Stormpath Web sites and provide related services such as fulfilling orders or providing customer service. When we supply your information to our partners and these third parties, we require them to use it only for the function they are helping us with. We do not sell, rent, or trade your personal information to any third parties, and we will not use your email address for unsolicited marketing.  
Stormpath may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Under such circumstances, Stormpath may be prohibited by law, court order or other legal process from providing notice of the disclosure, and we reserve the right to not provide such notice in its sole discretion.  
Stormpath may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including personal information, in connection with a merger, reorganization, or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. In such an event, your personal information may be transferred to and used by another company. If so, you will have the opportunity to ask not to receive promotional information following any change of control.

#### Access to Your Information:

You have the right to access and correct your personal information at any time. To review, update or make changes to your personal information, please send us an email to [info@stormpath.com](mailto:info@stormpath.com).

#### Third Party Sites

Our Web sites may contain links to other Web sites for news and other information. Our Privacy Policy only applies to the Stormpath Web sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites. You should check the privacy policies of those sites before providing your personal information to them. In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, Stormpath is potentially liable.

#### Security

We use physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, including firewall, encryption and password protection for our databases, designed to protect the security of the data collected and to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure to any of your information.

#### EU-US Privacy Shield Compliance

Stormpath complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Stormpath has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>  
In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, Stormpath commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact [compliance@stormpath.com](mailto:compliance@stormpath.com) OR

**Stormpath, Inc.**  
1825 S Grant Street, Ste 450  
San Mateo, CA 94402  
Attn: Compliance Dept.  

Under certain limited conditions, the individual can invoke “last resort” binding arbitration.

#### Contacting Us With Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact [info@stormpath.com](mailto:info@stormpath.com).

#### Transfer to and Use in the United States

Stormpath will transfer any personal information you provide to the United States of America to use and store the information for the purposes described herein. By using our Web sites and providing us with your personal information, you consent to such transfer, use, and storage of your personal information.

Stormpath is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and/or other U.S. authorized statutory bodies. Also, Stormpath may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
